SAIF **UDDIN**

saifuddin.uk



contact@saifuddin.uk



London, UK



Full Stack Web Developer

SUMMARY

A Front-End Web Developer, with **8 years of IT experience** and a Bachelors (BSc) in **Computer Game Development**. While I worked as an IT engineer I utilised my programmatic nature/skillset in order to modernise the way we work. I believe the most efficient way in which large quantities of work can be handled is with careful planning, programmatic thinking and commitment to reach milestones to keep stakeholders able to work & operations constantly improving. Looking to grow in a company as a Front End Developer.

EDUCATION

edX

Front End Web Development Bootcamp 2023 - 2024

University of East London

Bachelors (BSc) in Computer Game Development 2013 – 2017

SKILLS

- CSS3
- HTML5
- Gii
- BootStrap
- jQuery
- React.js
- Node.js
- Express.js

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

• JavaScript, C#, Java, C++, Python

CERTIFICATIONS

- edX Front End Dev Certificate (pending)
- Computer Game Development, BSc
- ITIL Foundation
- Mental Health First Aider



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Level 3 IT Support Analyst

AlphaSights | 2023 - 2023

- VIP support for the CEO and other senior executives.
- Presenting to stakeholders and engineers as a Scrum Master
- Tech stack: Google Workspace, Addigy, Cisco, Slack, Powershell

2nd Line Support Consultant

Shiseido UK | 2021 - 2023

- AV setup for video conferencing and presentations for global teams including stakeholders.
- Supported multiple sites including retail equipment such as: MPOS devices, tills, CCTV, Network patching and upgrades.
- Tech stack: AirWatch, Okta, Office 365, Ivanti, Box, PaperCut

Senior IT Desktop Engineer

Newham College of Further Education | 2019 - 2020

- Training mid and junior engineers.
- Low-level troubleshooting
- Providing support for 2 main sites and 8 remote sites
- Writing documentation for team members and guides for users
- Tech stack: Intune, Azure, Python/Shell scripting, Adobe, Cisco AnyConnect, Sharp/Canon/HP/Xerox printers, Office 365.

Service Support Engineer

Telegraph Media Group | 2017 - 2019

- 1st & 2nd Line support including on-call and VIP support.
- Supported multiple sites.
- AV support in the auditorium for presentations and conferences with internal and external stakeholders.
- Tech stack: G-Suite, Sophos AV, Citrix, JIRA, Okta, Adobe, AEM, Jamf, SCCM